export const quizQuestions_4 = {
  questions: [
  {
    question: 'What is a Single Page Application (SPA) in the context of web development?',
    choices: [
      'An application that loads multiple HTML pages for different routes',
      'An application that uses a single HTML page and updates the content dynamically',
      'An application that utilizes multiple server-side rendering techniques',
      'An application that only runs on mobile devices'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'An application that uses a single HTML page and updates the content dynamically'
  },
  {
    question: 'What purpose does a routing library serve in a React SPA?',
    choices: [
      'It helps optimize images and assets for faster loading',
      'It manages the state of components in React',
      'It enables navigation and rendering of different components based on the URL',
      'It restricts access to specific routes based on user authentication'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'It enables navigation and rendering of different components based on the URL'
  },
  {
    question: 'Which React library is commonly used for handling routing in SPAs?',
    choices: [
      'React Transition Group',
      'React Router',
      'Redux',
      'Axios'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'React Router'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of BrowserRouter in React Router?',
    choices: [
      'To handle asynchronous data fetching in React components',
      'To manage state changes in Redux',
      'To synchronize the UI with the URL',
      'To declare routes and their components'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To declare routes and their components'
  },
  {
    question: 'How can you define a route in React Router?',
    choices: [
      '<Route path="/about" component={About} />',
      '<Link href="/about" />',
      '<Navigate route="/about" component={About} />',
      '<RouteLink path="/about" component={About} />'
    ],
    correctAnswer: '<Route path="/about" component={About} />'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of Route component in React Router?',
    choices: [
      'To create a link between different components',
      'To define a specific URL path and map it to a component',
      'To handle user authentication',
      'To handle HTTP requests'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To define a specific URL path and map it to a component'
  },
  {
    question: 'How can you navigate to a different route in React Router programmatically?',
    choices: [
      'By using <Redirect /> component',
      'By calling the navigate() function',
      'By using window.location.href',
      'By setting state in the component'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'By calling the navigate() function'
  },
  {
    question: 'What does Switch component do in React Router?',
    choices: [
      'It switches between different states in a component',
      'It toggles between light and dark mode in the application',
      'It renders the first <Route> or <Redirect> that matches the current URL',
      'It enables navigation between different applications'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'It renders the first <Route> or <Redirect> that matches the current URL'
  },
  {
    question: 'What is the purpose of NavLink in React Router?',
    choices: [
      'To navigate between different applications',
      'To handle form submissions in React components',
      'To apply styles to the active link based on the current URL',
      'To connect React components to Redux store'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'To apply styles to the active link based on the current URL'
  },
  {
    question: 'Can you pass parameters to routes in React Router?',
    choices: [
      'Yes, by using query parameters only',
      'Yes, by using route parameters or query parameters',
      'No, React Router doesnâ€™t support passing parameters',
      'Parameters can only be passed via Redux'
    ],
    correctAnswer: 'Yes, by using route parameters or query parameters'
    },
  ],
}